{
    "subject": "resource/Code_Two",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "Code Two is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9191337823867798,
            "question": "Is Code Two a fictional or non-fictional type of film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8821941614151001,
            "question": "What makes a film classified as Code Two distinct from other types of films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7463725805282593,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Code Two films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6922633051872253,
            "question": "What is the target audience for Code Two films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6326353549957275,
            "question": "Who are some famous directors known for making Code Two films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6280263066291809,
            "question": "What kind of media is Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6137415170669556,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who have starred in Code Two films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.589486837387085,
            "question": "How has the popularity of Code Two films changed over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.511766791343689,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres within Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4804600179195404,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a Code Two?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Code Two is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_366_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any subgenres within Code Two?",
            "html": "dbpedia_366_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has the popularity of Code Two films changed over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_366_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any actors who have starred in Code Two films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_366_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_366_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents discuss \"Code Two,\" describing it as a movie, thus supporting the statement that \"Code Two is a type of Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}